deepyalla.com 2014-11-28

# Deepyalla Deep Links Directory - Human edited and SEO friendly . - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to the Deepyalla Directory Executive. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Deepyalla collects, and the ways in which Deepyalla uses that personal information.

## Personal information collection

Deepyalla may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including Google Analytics tracking the pages that are visited; 
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including Website Name, Description, Email Address;
  * information about transactions carried out over this website (including Link Payments; and
  * any other information that you send to Deepyalla.

## Using personal information

Deepyalla may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website; and
  * activate and supply products that you purchase;

Where Deepyalla discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Deepyalla may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

Deepyalla will never use the email for marketing nor will Deepyalla onsell any information provided.

## Securing your data

Deepyalla will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Deepyalla will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website are the responsibility of Paypal.

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that Deepyalla collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Deepyalla operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## Updating this statement

Deepyalla may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites.

Deepyalla is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## Contact Deepyalla

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Deepyalla's treatment of your personal information, please write to:

  * by email to admin@deepyalla.com; or
  * by post to 1204 Old North Crescent, Strathpine 4500 QLD Australia.

## About this privacy statement

This document is based on a free Contractology precedent available at [www.freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/). Contractology supply a wide variety of commercial legal documents, such as [precedent referral agreements](http://www.contractology.com/precedents/commission-agreement.html).
